dressupone.com 2019-09-04

# Privacy policy

Updated: May 29, 2017

Dressupone is committed to protect your privacy online. To further this commitment, we have adopted an online privacy policy that explains how we collect, store, and use information collected about you online. By using our website, you agree to observe and be bound by this Privacy Policy and you consent to the processing, collection, use and disclosure of your information in accordance with its terms. Please don't use our website if you don't agree with our Privacy Policy.

## Cookies

Dressupone use cookies to improve the use of our website. A cookie is a small file that websites store on your pc and this is an easy and convenient method for us to personalize your experience on our website. For example, cookies allow us to remember your screen name, tell us that you have visited our website before, and may contain information that will make your next visit to our website more enjoyable. Furthermore, Dressupone may use cookies and third party vendors to deliver ads related to our website to you while you are surfing other sites and use them to provide social media tools. 

**Cookies placed by third parties**  
Advertising displayed in our website may contain cookies placed by third parties including the advertising party itself. These positions are used to display third party ads and are reserved for advertiser to measure the effectiveness of its advertising campaign. These cookies are also used to recognise you when you browse other websites.

**Google Adsense and Google Analytics**  
We use Google's products to analyze and display ads on our website. For more information on how Google use your information and how to control your data sent to Google, please visit [this website](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/)

If you would like to opt-out google adsense, you may visit [this website](https://www.google.com/settings/ads) to opt-out directly with them.

If you would like to opt-out google analytics, you may visit [this website](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en) to opt-out directly with them.

**Cookies for sharing on social media**  
Our site may contain icons linked to social networks (such as Facebook, Twitter and Google Plus) so that you can share the site’s contents on social networks or give your opinion. Please note that your use of these social media services will be governed by the social networks terms and conditions and privacy policy. Our site has no control over these plug-ins and the procedures used by these social networks for collecting and handling your browsing data. You can look at these social networks privacy policy to learn more about your rights. 

If you would like to opt-out social media, you may visit [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217), [Twitter](https://twitter.com/privacy?lang=en), [Google Plus](https://www.google.com/intl/en_us/+/policy/pagesterm.html) to opt-out directly with them.

**Browsers**  
Most browser accept cookies but you can refuse all cookies and delete them anytime you want. We added a link for each browser to show you how to remove cookies in your browser.

Internet Explorer  
Here is the [link](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/278835/how-to-delete-cookie-files-in-internet-explorer) to manage cookies with Internet Explorer.

Microsoft Edge  
Here is the [link](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy) to manage cookies with Microsoft Edge.

Google Chrome  
Here is the [link](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?co=GENIE.Platform%3DDesktop&hl=en) to manage cookies with Google Chrome. 

Mozilla Firefox  
Here is the [link](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/delete-cookies-remove-info-websites-stored) to manage cookies with Mozilla Firefox. 

If you would like to opt-out of such ads, you may visit networkadvertising.org/choices to opt-out of such use of cookies. 

## User Provided Information

Personal information is information that enables an individual person to be identified either directly or indirectly.

The personal information collected on our website is the result of freely given information communicated via the forms that exist on the website.

This personal information that is given upon registration is, where applicable, taken and handled for the following purposes: to validate your registration and to manage your account. This information will only be used to recognize you when you return on our website. Some information, such as the IP address and user-agent may be automatically collected. Dressupone may disclose information to third parties in special cases, such as when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with Dressupone's property, visitors, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities or to comply with the law, applicable regulations, governmental and quasi-governmental requests, court orders or subpoenas.

The company undertakes not use the information collected for any purpose other than that for which it was intended when collected.

## Intellectual property

Our Site, its overall structure and its graphics, texts, images, sounds and videos that make up this structure, are the property of the Publisher. The entire Site is governed by French and international legislation relating to copyright and intellectual property. Any representation, reproduction, publication or any use whatsoever and any partial or total exploitation of its contents (including brands, logos, software, information, data, texts, illustrations, photographs, banners, tabs, pop-ups, music or any other distinguishing sign) and services made available by the Site regardless of the procedure is strictly forbidden without the prior written authorisation of the Publisher, and may constitute counterfeit in the sense conveyed by Articles L335-2 and subsequent texts of the French Intellectual Property Code.

Where applicable, the User expressly and willingly concedes to the Publisher all intellectual property rights relating to messages and contents that the User publishes on the Site, particularly in relation to the right to reproduce, represent and adapt content on any media support and in any format presently known and not yet known at this time and through any system and on any network including the Internet, throughout the world and in perpetuity.

## Security

We are concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your information. We provide physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect information we process and maintain. For example, we limit access to this information to authorized employees and contractors who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our website. Please be aware that, although we endeavor provide reasonable security for information we process and maintain, no security system can prevent all potential security breaches.

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, we don't have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide when you visit such sites and other websites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should look at the privacy policy applicable to the website directly.

## Changes

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason. We will notify you of any changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy here and informing you via email. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes, as continued use is deemed approval of all changes.

## Contact us

If you have any questions regarding privacy while using our website, or have questions about our practices, please contact us via email at support@bwebmedia.eu.
